

(330) 819-8327 www.lindseystanek.com hello@lindseystanek.com

Summary of Qualifications

I am a front end web developer with over 5 years of experience. I focus on emerging web technologies and creating mobile optimized websites and web applications. I enjoy being part of the entire process, starting with researching, brainstorming and wireframing to implementation, troubleshooting and analytics. I love learning through challenges and taking educated risks.

Skills and Competencies

HTML/CSS
AngularJS
Responsive Design/Development
Conducting Learning Sessions

Sass/LESS
Git
REST APIs
Dev Team Management

JavaScript/jQuery
UX/UI
Adobe Creative Suite
CMS Experience

Experience

Senior eCommerce Front End Web Developer — DICK'S Sporting Goods

July 2016 - Present

- Manage team of associate web developers on the day-to-day projects for the DICK'S Sporting Goods site
- · Conduct and manage code review sessions among the team to improve code quality
- · Work closely with the UI design team to produce engaging web experiences
- · Lead lunch & learns to teach the rest of our development team skills such as AngularJS
- Conceptualize, plan and build web apps using HTML, Sass, JavaScript/jQuery, AngularJS and RESTful APIs
- Worked on setting up Continuous Integration scripts for deployments
- · Work within the Management Center CMS tool and increase efficiency using this tool
- Discuss technical capabilities the front-end dev team is able to produce to our stakeholders
- Develop landing pages for multi-million dollar seasonal campaigns
- · Assisted in the development & UAT of a new platform for the DICK'S Sporting Goods site

eCommerce Front End Web Developer — DICK'S Sporting Goods

May 2015 - July 2016

- Conceptualize, plan and build web apps using HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery and APIs to streamline processes
- Build landing pages for multi-million dollar seasonal campaigns
- · Build marketing sites for in-house brands to be pixel-perfect based off of designs
- Help build & maintain various WordPress marketing sites
- Maintain content for dickssportinggoods.com
- Suggest and develop enhancements to current processes for the various DSG owned websites
- Ensure browser compatibility for DSG websites all the way back to IE7

Front End Web Designer/Developer, Digital Commerce - Giant Eagle

April 2013 - May 2015

- Rebuilt entire website's front end using the inuit.css grid, Sass, HTML5 and CSS3
- Plan, wireframe, design & develop new front end initiatives, including one-off promotional landing pages and online ordering programs
- · Helped plan, wireframe, design & build a mobile-friendly eCommerce site
- · Built responsive microsites using Bootstrap 3 and LESS
- Work with back-end offshore developers on bugs and troubleshooting
- Perform web updates & manage products among the different Content Management Systems (such as SiteCore & Episerver) for the various brands and departments
- · Design and develop responsive email campaigns from the ground up
- Design and develop Facebook contests, sweepstakes and other applications
- Led in-depth CMS training sessions to newer and less experienced users
- Brainstorm ways to make current processes more efficient & up-to-date with competitors



(330) 819-8327 www.lindseystanek.com hello@lindseystanek.com

Experience Continued

Web Developer - Levy MG

January 2012 - April 2013

- · Design/develop websites for a variety of clients and industries
- Maintain existing websites and client relationships
- Take educated risks by using new technologies
- · Design/develop email blasts
- Interface with clients to efficiently market their industrial business online

Freelance Web Designer & Developer - NV Studios

February 2013

- Designed entire brand including logo, business cards, CD labels and website
- Designed and developed a vertical scrolling website using HTML5 & CSS3 technologies

Freelance Web Designer & Developer - Daniel K. Haas Photography

December 2012

- Designed and developed a simple, clean photography website in WordPress
- Ensured easy updating ability for client to upload his own images, blog posts, etc.

Education 3.9 GPA

The Art Institute of Pittsburgh

March 2013

Bachelor of Science degree in Web Design and Interactive Media

Awards

- · Best In Graduation Portfolio Show
- President's List
- · National Technical Honor Society

- · Student of the Quarter
- Dean's List
- Perfect Attendance

References and examples of work available upon request